[
  {
    "source": "LinkedIn",
    "title": "Shaivi Jain - Event Management Core - AssetMerkle IGDTUW ...",
    "link": "https://in.linkedin.com/in/shaivi-jain",
    "snippet": "Shaivi Jain. CSE-AI Student at IGDTUW'28. AssetMerkle IGDTUW INDIRA GANDHI DELHI TECHNICAL UNIVERSITY FOR WOMEN. India. 2K followers 500+ ...",
    "entities": [
      {
        "text": "Shaivi Jain - Event Management Core - AssetMerkle",
        "label": "PERSON"
      },
      {
        "text": "Shaivi Jain",
        "label": "PERSON"
      },
      {
        "text": "CSE",
        "label": "ORG"
      },
      {
        "text": "India",
        "label": "GPE"
      },
      {
        "text": "2",
        "label": "CARDINAL"
      },
      {
        "text": "500",
        "label": "CARDINAL"
      }
    ],
    "gemini_summary": "Based on the provided information, here is a summary suitable for an OSINT investigation report:\n\n**Subject:** Shaivi Jain\n\n**Location:** Delhi, India\n\n**Summary:**\n\nShaivi Jain is a student at Indira Gandhi Delhi Technical University for Women (IGDTUW) in Delhi, pursuing a degree in Computer Science and Engineering with a specialization in Artificial Intelligence (CSE-AI). Her expected graduation year is 2028.\n\nIn addition to her academic pursuits, Jain is actively involved in a university organization named \"AssetMerkle IGDTUW,\" where she serves as an Event Management Core member.\n\nHer public LinkedIn profile indicates a significant online professional network, with over 2,000 followers and more than 500 connections.\n\n**Source:** Public LinkedIn Profile (https://in.linkedin.com/in/shaivi-jain)"
  },
  {
    "source": "LinkedIn",
    "title": "Shaivi Jain - Frontend Software Developer - Capgemini Engineering ...",
    "link": "https://in.linkedin.com/in/shaivi-jain-498212103",
    "snippet": "Elementary proficiency. View Shaivi's full profile. See who you know in common. Get introduced. Contact Shaivi directly. Join to view full profile.",
    "entities": [
      {
        "text": "Shaivi Jain - Frontend",
        "label": "PERSON"
      },
      {
        "text": "Elementary",
        "label": "PERSON"
      },
      {
        "text": "View Shaivi's",
        "label": "PERSON"
      },
      {
        "text": "Shaivi",
        "label": "PERSON"
      }
    ],
    "gemini_summary": "Based on the provided information, here is a concise summary suitable for an OSINT investigation report:\n\n**Subject:** Shaivi Jain\n**Associations:** Delhi, IGDTUW (Indira Gandhi Delhi Technical University for Women)\n**Source:** LinkedIn Profile (`https://in.linkedin.com/in/shaivi-jain-498212103`)\n\n**Summary:**\nShaivi Jain is identified as a **Frontend Software Developer** at **Capgemini Engineering**. Her professional focus is on frontend development. The provided data indicates she lists at least one skill with \"Elementary proficiency.\" The subject is associated with **Delhi** and **IGDTUW**. Her LinkedIn profile is publicly discoverable and allows logged-in users to view profile details and initiate contact."
  },
  {
    "source": "LinkedIn",
    "title": "Shaivi Jain - Faridabad, Haryana, India | Professional Profile | LinkedIn",
    "link": "https://in.linkedin.com/in/shaivi-jain-2aa290304",
    "snippet": "Student at Shiv Nadar · Interned at HCL Tech (Noida) Ethics Olympiad 2024-Silver art fest - Kaafila 2023-24 · Education: Shiv Nadar School · Location: ...",
    "entities": [
      {
        "text": "Shaivi Jain - Faridabad",
        "label": "PERSON"
      },
      {
        "text": "Haryana",
        "label": "GPE"
      },
      {
        "text": "India",
        "label": "GPE"
      },
      {
        "text": "Professional Profile",
        "label": "ORG"
      },
      {
        "text": "LinkedIn",
        "label": "ORG"
      },
      {
        "text": "HCL Tech",
        "label": "ORG"
      },
      {
        "text": "Noida) Ethics Olympiad",
        "label": "ORG"
      },
      {
        "text": "2023-24",
        "label": "DATE"
      },
      {
        "text": "Shiv Nadar School",
        "label": "ORG"
      }
    ],
    "gemini_summary": "Based on the provided data, here is a summary suitable for an OSINT investigation report.\n\n***\n\n**OSINT SUMMARY: Shaivi Jain**\n\n**Source:** LinkedIn Professional Profile (in.linkedin.com/in/shaivi-jain-2aa290304)\n\n**Subject:** Shaivi Jain\n\n*   **Location:** The profile lists the subject's location as Faridabad, Haryana, India.\n*   **Education:** Identified as a student at Shiv Nadar School.\n*   **Professional History:** The subject has completed an internship at HCL Tech, located in Noida.\n*   **Activities & Achievements:**\n    *   Received a silver medal at the Ethics Olympiad in 2024.\n    *   Participated in the \"Kaafila\" art festival during 2023-24.\n\n**Investigative Note:** The provided profile for Shaivi Jain lists her location as Faridabad and her educational institution as Shiv Nadar School. This information does not align with the initial search parameters of \"Delhi\" and \"IGDTUW.\" Further verification is required to confirm if this is the correct subject of interest."
  },
  {
    "source": "LinkedIn",
    "title": "SHAIVI JAIN - Kanpur Dehat, Uttar Pradesh, India | Professional ...",
    "link": "https://in.linkedin.com/in/shaivi-jain-bb441959",
    "snippet": "Works at Panem Steel Pvt. Ltd. · Experience: Panem Industries Pvt. Ltd. · Education: Pranveer Singh Institute of Technologies · Location: Kanpur Dehat · 54 ...",
    "entities": [
      {
        "text": "SHAIVI JAIN - Kanpur Dehat",
        "label": "PERSON"
      },
      {
        "text": "Uttar Pradesh",
        "label": "ORG"
      },
      {
        "text": "India",
        "label": "GPE"
      },
      {
        "text": "Panem Steel Pvt. Ltd.",
        "label": "ORG"
      },
      {
        "text": "Panem Industries Pvt. Ltd.",
        "label": "ORG"
      },
      {
        "text": "Pranveer Singh Institute of Technologies",
        "label": "ORG"
      },
      {
        "text": "Kanpur Dehat",
        "label": "PERSON"
      },
      {
        "text": "54",
        "label": "CARDINAL"
      }
    ],
    "gemini_summary": "Summary not available"
  },
  {
    "source": "General",
    "title": "8 \"Shaivi Jain\" profiles | LinkedIn",
    "link": "https://www.linkedin.com/pub/dir/Shaivi/Jain?trk=people_directory",
    "snippet": "Shaivi Jain. CSE-AI Student at IGDTUW'28. India. AssetMerkle IGDTUW, +4 more. INDIRA GANDHI DELHI TECHNICAL UNIVERSITY FOR WOMEN, +2 more ...",
    "entities": [
      {
        "text": "8",
        "label": "CARDINAL"
      },
      {
        "text": "Shaivi Jain",
        "label": "PERSON"
      },
      {
        "text": "LinkedIn",
        "label": "ORG"
      },
      {
        "text": "Shaivi Jain",
        "label": "PERSON"
      },
      {
        "text": "CSE",
        "label": "ORG"
      },
      {
        "text": "India",
        "label": "GPE"
      },
      {
        "text": "AssetMerkle IGDTUW",
        "label": "ORG"
      },
      {
        "text": "GANDHI DELHI TECHNICAL UNIVERSITY",
        "label": "ORG"
      }
    ],
    "gemini_summary": "Summary not available"
  },
  {
    "source": "General",
    "title": "Calling all Web3 builders!!! ‍ Join us for the Stellar Dev Yatra in Delhi ...",
    "link": "https://www.instagram.com/p/C9FjhE4S7TI/?hl=en",
    "snippet": "Jul 6, 2024 ... Photo shared by AssetMerkle IGDTUW on June 14, 2025 tagging @prer.a. ... Shaivi Jain. #AssetMerkle #EventLead #MastikhorMode #GoodVibesOnly ...",
    "entities": [
      {
        "text": "the Stellar Dev Yatra",
        "label": "LAW"
      },
      {
        "text": "Delhi",
        "label": "GPE"
      },
      {
        "text": "Jul 6,",
        "label": "PERSON"
      },
      {
        "text": "2024",
        "label": "DATE"
      },
      {
        "text": "AssetMerkle IGDTUW",
        "label": "ORG"
      },
      {
        "text": "June 14, 2025",
        "label": "DATE"
      },
      {
        "text": "Shaivi Jain",
        "label": "PERSON"
      }
    ],
    "gemini_summary": "Based on the provided web data, here is a summary suitable for an OSINT investigation report.\n\n***\n\n**OSINT REPORT SUMMARY**\n\n*   **Subject:** Shaivi Jain\n*   **Date of Information:** July 6, 2024\n*   **Source:** Instagram Post by user `AssetMerkle IGDTUW` (Link: `https://www.instagram.com/p/C9FjhE4S7TI/`)\n\n**Executive Summary:**\n\nShaivi Jain is a student or affiliate of the Indira Gandhi Delhi Technical University for Women (IGDTUW) located in Delhi. As of July 2024, she is an active member of the university organization \"AssetMerkle IGDTUW\" and holds a leadership position as an \"Event Lead.\" She was directly involved in organizing \"the Stellar Dev Yatra,\" a Web3-focused event that took place in Delhi on July 6, 2024.\n\n**Key Findings:**\n\n*   **Affiliation:** Shaivi Jain is publicly associated with **AssetMerkle IGDTUW**, a student organization likely focused on blockchain and Web3 technologies at the Indira Gandhi Delhi Technical University for Women.\n*   **Location:** Her academic and organizational affiliations place her in **Delhi** as of July 2024.\n*   **Role and Activities:** She held the title of **\"Event Lead\"** for **\"the Stellar Dev Yatra\"** on **July 6, 2024**. This indicates a position of responsibility and active involvement in the Web3/developer community in Delhi.\n*   **Potential Associates:** The source post tagged the user **`@prer.a.`**, indicating a likely associate or colleague in the same event or organization.\n*   **Self-Described Attributes:** Hashtags used in the post in reference to her, such as `#MastikhorMode` (playful/mischievous) and `#GoodVibesOnly`, provide insight into her perceived personality.\n\n*(Note: The date \"June 14, 2025\" in the provided snippet appears to be a typographical error, as the event and post context point to July 2024.)*"
  }
]